https://www.upcounsel.com/privacy-policy-template

Privacy Policy Template
Startup Law ResourcesIncorporateBusiness Operations
This privacy policy is to be used as the beginning of a more robust privacy policy for a website with user generated content. The purpose of privacy policy to inform your users how you will use the information they contribute to your site, especially personal information.
Share this document
Download for free
The Best Lawyers For Less
Hire the top business lawyers and save up to 60% on legal fees
Post a Job
Trusted By
Content Approvedby UpCounsel
Popular Cities
Atlanta Intellectual Property Lawyers
Austin Intellectual Property Lawyers
Boston Intellectual Property Lawyers
Chicago Intellectual Property Lawyers
View All Intellectual Property Lawyers
Want High Quality, Transparent, and Affordable Legal Services?
Get Free Proposals
Request Free Proposals
Download Document
x
Register with Google
Welcome
First Name
Last Name
City
Located in the U.S.?
Select Country
Afghanistan
Albania
Algeria
American Samoa
Andorra
Angola
Anguilla
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Islas Malvinas)
Faroe Islands
Fiji
Finland
France
French Guiana
French Polynesia
French Southern and Antarctic Lands
Gabon
Haiti
Holy See (Vatican City)
Honduras
Hong Kong (SAR)
Hungary
Iceland
India
Indonesia
Iran
Iraq
Ireland
Israel
Zip Code
Not located in the U.S.?
Work Email
Phone Number
Optional, will help us get you started faster
Are you a lawyer?
Yes, In-House Counsel
Yes, Sole Practitioner / Law Firm
No, I'm not a lawyer
Next
Are you interested in sourcing clients on UpCounsel?
Yes
No
Select Your Main Practice Areas
Business Formation & Structure
Commercial Contracts
Debt & Bankruptcy
Immigration
Labor & Employment
Customize This Document to Better Protect You
LEGAL NOTICE: We strongly suggest you have this document customized to your unique situation, because you might require additional clause(s) to better protect your business from potential legal issues.
Ensure You Are Protected. Get Legal Peace of Mind.
Get Free Attorney Quotes Today
SATISFACTION GUARANTEEDOn All jobs booked with a verified attorney and paid for over UpCounsel.
Customize This Document to Better Protect You
LEGAL NOTICE: We strongly suggest you customize this document to suit you or your client's unique situation. You may require additional clause(s) to better protect you or your client’s business from potential legal issues.
Want to grow your practice?
Learn More
Create your profile today and gain access to free marketing and practice management tools. Once your profile is complete, you will be reviewed for the UpCounsel Marketplace where approved attorneys can find and manage new or existing clients, backed by the UpCounsel guarantee.
We Are Sending You This Document Now
LEGAL NOTICE: We strongly suggest you have this document customized to your unique situation, because you might require additional clause(s) to better protect your business from potential legal issues.
Ensure You Are Protected. Get Legal Peace of Mind.
Get Free Attorney Quotes Today
SATISFACTION GUARANTEEDOn All jobs booked with a verified attorney and paid for over UpCounsel.
If you do not see an email from UpCounsel in the next few minutes, please check your spam box. Add: noreply@upcounsel.com to your email address book. This will help ensure future email delivery.
We Are Sending You This Document Now
LEGAL NOTICE: We strongly suggest you customize this document to suit you or your client's unique situation. You may require additional clause(s) to better protect you or your client’s business from potential legal issues.
Want to grow your practice?
Learn More
Create your profile today and gain access to free marketing and practice management tools. Once your profile is complete, you will be reviewed for the UpCounsel Marketplace where approved attorneys can find and manage new or existing clients, backed by the UpCounsel guarantee.
If you do not see an email from UpCounsel in the next few minutes, please check your spam box. Add: noreply@upcounsel.com to your email address book. This will help ensure future email delivery.
Share this document
Send to your friends, partners or attorney.
Your Name:
Your Email:
Email Addresses:
(separated by a comma, 10 max)
Message Body:
Send a copy to myself
Cancel
Send
